Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- Wray, Anthony, Sex Nuts, Phenix Publishers, LL 786, 1968 (Box 44)
- Wright, L. B., Queer Street, Private Editions Books, PE 355, 1965 (Box 48)
- Wright, Richard, Eight Men, Avon Books, G-1087, 1957 (Box 92)
- Wright, Stephen, Different, Bantam Books, 553-08382, 1974 (Box 6)
- Wynters, Rob, Wynter's Tail, Surrey House, MH 420, 1973 (Box 81)
- Wynters, Rob, Wynter's Balls, Surrey House, MH 431, 1973 (Box 81)
- Young, Dalene, Alexander: The Other Side of Dawn, Ballantine Books, 345-25770-7-150, 1977 (Box 95)
- Young, Karl, Where Eagles Pair, F.S. Publishing, GPL 104, n.d. (Box 17)
- Young, Karl, Four On The Floor, F.S. Publishing, GW 106, n.d. (Box 18)
- Young, Karl, Suddenly It's Speed, F.S. Publishing, GW 112, n.d. (Box 18)
- Young, Karl, New Member, XXX Inc, GW 117, 1971 (Box 18)
- Young, Karl, Guess Who's Up In The Loft, XXX Inc., GW 128, n.d. (Box 18)
- Young, Perry Deane, The David Kopay Story, Bantam Books, 0-555-11162-0, 1977 (Box 5)
- Young, Phillip, Big Chuck, Spade Publishing, SP-62, n.d. (Box 58)
- Yuma, Gary, Flesh Probe, Eros Publishing, GGS-106, 1973 (Box 16)
- Zachary, John, Sex Studio, Regency, 1024, 1970 (Box 54)
- Zola, Emile, Nana, Pocket Books, 104, 1941 (Box 4)
- Zupp, Peter, My Friend Larry, 101 Enterprises, Inc., -0-, 1969 (Box 95)